savemoney.my 2012-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Save Money Malaysia |SaveMoney.my

Saving Experts Sdn. Bhd. (“we” or “us”) owns and operates this website and we take your privacy very seriously. This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for this website and should be read together with our **Terms of Use**.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE **TERMS OF USE**. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, PLEASE EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS THE WEBSITE.

We are ready to address your questions and concerns regarding this policy and our privacy practices. If you would like to contact us, please do so via email at support@savemoney.my

**1.        ****Types and Uses of Collected Information**

****a. **Personally Identifiable Information.** We define Personally Identifiable Information as information that identifies a specific user. When you engage in certain activities on the website, such as subscribing to our email newsletter, creating an account, submitting content and/or posting content in discussion forums, requesting information about our services, taking part in a survey, entering a contest or sweepstakes sponsored by us or our partners, submitting a review, sending us or our partners feedback, applying for a job vacancy, posting a video or signing up for special offers from third parties through the website (collectively known as “Identification Activities”), we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. It is optional for you to engage in an Identification Activity. Should you elect to engage in an Identification Activity, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information about yourself, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including your postal code), email address, telephone number and date of birth. Subject to the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some is identified as voluntary. If the mandatory information for a particular activity is not provided upon request, you will not be permitted to engage in that activity.

We use Personally Identifiable Information to provide information to you, enhance the operation of the Website, administer sweepstakes and contests (though there won’t be many), improve our marketing and promotional efforts, and analyze and improve the overall Website. Aside from that, if you use our Website to send information or a product to another person, we may store your personal information. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot, accomplish administrative tasks, get in touch with you, enforce our agreements with you, including our Website Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, comply with applicable Malaysian law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities.

b.  **Non-Personally Identifiable Information.** We define Non-Personally Identifiable Information as information that does not identify a specific End User. Like many other Websites, the Website automatically collects certain non-identifiable information regarding Website users, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer, the IP address of your Internet Service Provider, the date and time you access the Web Site, the Internet address of the Website from which you linked directly to the Website, the operating system you are using, the sections of the Web Site you visit, the Website pages accessed and information viewed, and the materials you post to or download from the Website. This non-identifiable information is used for our Website and system administration purposes as well as to improve the Website. We, and/or our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers, may automatically collect this information when you visit our Website through the use of electronic tools such as Cookies.

We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to provide statistical information about the usage of our site, administer the Website, troubleshoot, analyze trends, gather general demographic data, and comply with relevant Malaysian law.

****2\. Release of Personally Identifiable Information****

********We will not share or sell your Personally Identifiable Information with other parties except as provided below:

a. As with any company, we could be involved with a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets. Your Personally Identifiable Information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of ours or that acquirer’s assets may continue to process your Personally Identifiable Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

b. We may share your information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary for our Protection and the Protection of Others. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website. You hereby consent to us sharing your Personally Identifiable Information under the circumstances described herein.

**3\. Release of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

****We may disclose or share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Affiliates and Third Party Service Providers, and Third Party Advertisers. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information with “Third Party Advertisers” or “Third Party Advertising Companies”.

We may use Third Party Advertising Companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to this Website and visits to other websites or locations in order to provide, through the use of network tags, advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

We also use Third Party Service Providers to track and analyze Non-Personally Identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our users to administer our Website, in order to constantly improve their quality. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes or as a representative audience for Third Party Advertisers. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned and used by us.

**4\. Security of Information**

****We use reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. Unfortunately, no one can guarantee 100% security. If you have particular security concerns about certain personal information, please do not transmit that information over the Internet. You accept the inherent risks of providing information and dealing online and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security.

**5\. Privacy Policies of Third Party Websites**

****This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on SaveMoney.my. Our website contains links to third party websites that have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Therefore, if you link to any such website, we urge you review the website’s privacy policy as we cannot be held responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

**6\. Changes**

****In Saving Experts Sdn. Bhd.’s sole discretion, we may, from time to time make changes to this privacy policy to reflect any changes to our privacy practices in accordance with changes to legislation, best practice or website enhancements. We will let you know what these changes are by posting them to this page, but it is your responsibility as a user to make sure that you are aware of them, by checking for any changes on a regular basis. Changes will become effective as soon as they are posted and your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**7\. Contact Us**

****If you have any feedback or queries regarding your personal information and our Privacy Policy, please contact us by writing to:

Saving Experts Sdn. Bhd.  
D-3A-10 Southgate Commercial Centre  
2 Jalan Dua off Jalan Chan Sow Lin  
55200 Kuala Lumpur  
This Privacy Policy was last modified on 25 February 2012.
